I'm a huge Zelda fan
It's not my favorite franchise of all time
but it's definitely in the top 40.
Before I make my Majora's mask review
I wanted to make a top Zelda facts list
but there are so many already and
they pretty much cover everything
every fact in existence.
But I found new facts that you didn't know.
So, here are the top 5 Zelda facts
I totally didn't make up 10 minutes ago.
In the orignal Zelda, the hero's name
was actually Zelda the entire time
But because of the Entertainment System's
inability to render commas,
and because the game was about saving the princess
everyone thought that her name was Zelda.
This also happent to Miss Metroid
and Lylatwars MacLoud
The official Zelda's time line splits into three
after Zelda Ocarina of time :
1 - Link is defeated at the end
2 - Link is victorious and becomes a child
3 - He is victorious and stays an adult
But Miyamoto has acknowledged that
there is in fact a fourth time line
Where at the start of the game Link tells Navy :
« Ten more minutes »
then scratches his balls and goes back to sleep
causing him to miss the entire adventure.
This causes Zelda to realize no one is coming.
And she decides to solve the problem herself.
She puts magically enchanted laxative in Ganon's wine,
causing him to have such
a massive and mighty diarrhea
that the bards will write songs about it.
Out of embarrassment,
Ganon goes home and never returns.
This leads to Link and the faces of evil.
Speaking of the Philips CD-i's games
are they the worst ever?
NoooOOOOooo.
When the first two Philips Zelda games came out,
they were actually compared
to the original Godfather movies.
Nintendo really didn't like this
so they launched an campaign
compared to nothing else in history,
where they would trash-talked the game
every chance they got
And even till this day they still bribe youtubers
to smack talk the game.
Notice how they only talk
about the mediocre animations
and they never talk about the story.
Which is a multi-layered emotional roller coaster.
Do you like the Gorons?
Then you might also like…
Quebec!
as it was the main inspiration for them
Don't believe me?
Then what if I told you that the Gorons come from a
special state province in a massive country to the north.
Still not sure?
Well… lets compare them!
Both the Goron's home country and Quebec are…
mountainous volcanic wastelands
Both have problems with giant fire-breathing lizards.
And to move faster,
the Gorons curl-up into a ball and roll.
The same with these fellas.
Still don't believe me?
Well done!
You're an ignorant asshole!
and you don't know shit.
Did you know that it was the Ocarina of Time dungeon
designer Eiji Aonuma that directed Majora's Mask?
It was going to be an expansion to Ocarina,
but he complained to Miyamoto
because he wanted to do a full game.
Miyamoto challenged him to create
a complete game in only 18 months.
Everyone said it was impossible,
but then, 17 months later…
He had nothing…
Not a single line of code had been written.
Eiji decided that he had to ask the devil for help.
He drew a demonic circle in his office.
He stood on it and said :
[Eiji] : « Lucifer, I have taken an impossible task.
I need thy help to finish it. »
The circle began to glow.
Eiji could feel the presence of the great beast, but dared not look at him.
The devil said :
[Lucifer] : « Oh… another Zelda developer… »
Eiji was confused
[Eiji] : « Another Zelda developer ? »
[Lucifer] : « I'll tell you what I told Miyamoto,
I will help you if you put me… in the game. »
And Eiji looked up.
And the game was made in time.
Now you might be asking :
« Why haven't I heard of any of this facts ? »
Well… it's because you're not a true a Zelda fan like me.
If you're interesting in more Zelda facts
you should probably Bing-it yourself you lazy wanker.
And that is the Kilian Experience
Check out my parody reviews, and if you're interested in my Majora's Mask review, you should subscribe.
Unless you have subscribe then you…
like… [mumbling] I don't know.